ningmp3.com 2013-08-06

# Privacy Policy

### Data Collected

_Browsing the Website._ You can access the Website without having an account, in which case only your IP address, country of origin and other non-personal information about your computer or device (such as web requests, browser type, browser language, referring URL, operating system and date and time of requests) will be recorded for log file information, aggregated traffic information and in the event that there is any misappropriation of information and/or content. 

_Registering on the Website._ Registration of an account is required for certain features on the Website. We require the following personal information at the time of registration: your username and password (which you generate), e-mail address, IP address and country of origin. Your username and country of origin may become publicly accessible on the Website. 

_Usage Information._ We may record information about your usage of the Website such as your use of the Website, the mp3s you search and listen to, the frequency and size of data transfers and other statistics. If you have registered and are logged in, we may associate that information with your account. 

_Uploaded Content._ Any personal information or content you voluntarily disclose online, including music and comments, becomes publicly available and may be collected and used by others. 

_Correspondences._ We may keep a record of any correspondence between you and us. 

_Cookies._ When you use the Website, we may send cookies to your computer to uniquely identify your browser session. We may use both session cookies and persistent cookies. 

### Data Usage

We may use your information to provide you with certain features and to create a personalized experience on the Website. We may also use that information to operate, maintain and improve features and functionality of the Website. 

We will not use your e-mail address or other personal information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent. We may use your e-mail without further consent for any purposes, including without limitation, commercial, marketing and administrative purposes. 

We use cookies, web beacons and other information to store information so that you will not have to re-enter it on future visits, provide personalized content and information, monitor the effectiveness of the Website and monitor aggregate metrics such as the number of visitors and page views (including for use in monitoring visitors from affiliates). They may also be used to provide targeted advertising based on your country of origin and other personal information. 

We may aggregate your personal information with personal information of other members and users, and disclose such information to advertisers and other third-parties for marketing and promotional purposes. 

Your username may be displayed to other users alongside Content you make available. 

Any Content that you submit may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels and may be viewed by the general public. 

### Disclosures of Information

We may be required to release certain data to comply with legal obligations or in order to enforce our Terms of Use and other agreements. We may also release certain data to protect the rights, property or safety of us, our users and others. This includes providing information to other companies or organizations like the police or governmental authorities for the purposes of protection against or prosecution of any illegal activity, whether or not it is identified in the Terms of Use. 

If you upload any illegal material to the Website, we may forward all available information to relevant authorities, including respective copyright owners, without any notice to you. 

### Miscellaneous

If you have an account on the Website and have a password giving you access to certain parts of the Website, you are responsible for keeping the password confidential. Anyone else with your password may access your account and other personal information. 

While we use commercially reasonable physical, managerial and technical safeguards to secure your information, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure and we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information or Content you transmit to us. Any information or Content you transmit to us is done at your own risk.
